OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 23) 6178/023
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Code no.8653: Sheet Metal Contractors Association of Philadelphia and Vicinity and Sheet Metal Workers International Association Local 19, 2007-2010 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Code no.8664: Associated General Contactors and Construction Contractors Labor Employers of New Jersey and International Union of Operating Engineers, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Code no.8699: Great Lakes Fabricators and Erectors Association, Associated General Contractors of America, Michigan Conveyor Manufacturers and International Association of Bridge, Structure, Reinforcing and Ornamental Iron Workers Local 25, 2007-2010 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Code no.8714: International Association of Bridge, Structure, Ornamental and Reinforcing Iron Workers and Trade Employers Bargaining Association of new Jersey and Independent Contractors, 2008-2011 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Code no.8719: Great Lakes Fabricators and Erectors Association and International Union of Operating Engineers Local 342 and 342A, 2007- 2010 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Code no.8734: Mechanical Contractors Association of Eastern Pennsylvania and Plumbers Local 690, 2005-2009 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Code no.8741: Iron Workers Local 25 International Association of Bridge, Structural, Ornamental and Reinforcing Iron Workers and Great Lakes Fabricators & Erectors Association, 2007-2010 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Code no.8746: Long Island Contractors Association and Building Material Teamsters Local 282 International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 2008- 2011 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Code no.8748: International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 282 Demolition, Debris, Asbestos Removal and Toxic Waste Agreement, 2005- 2008 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Code no.8750: Building Material Teamsters Local 282, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Building Material Suppliers Industry Memorandum of Agreement, 2008-2011 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Code no.8753: Contactors' Association of Greater New York and International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 282, 2005-2008 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Code no.8754: International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 282 and Signatories to the 2002-2005 Nassau- Suffolk Ready Mix Concrete and Sand & Gravel Agreement, 2008-2011 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Code no.8763: IBEW Local 349 and South Florida Chapter of National Electrical Contractors Association, 2007-2010 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Code no.8767: Laborers' International Union of North America Local 423 and Central Ohio Division Association General Contractors of America, 2005-2008 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Code no.8782: Building Contractors Association and International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 282, 2005-2008 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Code no.8788: Ohio Contractors Association and the Operative Plasterers' and Cement Masons' International Association of the United States and Canada, 2007-2010 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Code no.8799: Ohio Contactors Association and Ohio Conference of teamsters of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 2007- 2010 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Code no.8800: New Mexico Building Branch, Associated General Contractors and Southwest Regional Council of Carpenters, 2007- 2010 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Code no.8802: New Mexico Building Branch, Associated General Contractors and The New Mexico and Southwest Laborers' District Council, 2007-2010 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Code no.8811: Contactors Association of Pennsylvania and Great Pennsylvania Regional Council of Carpenters, United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners and Heavy & Highway Construction Workers Local 158, 2008-2012 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Code no.8813: Contractors Association of Eastern Pennsylvania and Laborers District Council of the Metropolitan Area of Philadelphia and Vicinity, 2006-2009 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Code no.8816: Contractors Association of Eastern Pennsylvania and Operative Plasterers and Cement Masons International Association of the United States and Canada, 2006-2009 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Code no.8829: General Building Laborers' Local Union 66 and Unnamed Employer, 2008-2011 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Code no.8902: Constructors' Labor Council of West Virginia and International Association of Bridge, Structural, Ornamental and reinforcing Ironworkers, 2007-2009 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Code no.8910: International Association of Bridge, Structural, Ornamental and Reinforcing Iron Workers Local 512 and Associated General Contractors of Minnesota and Minnesota Steel Erectors Association, 2004-2007 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Code no.8912: Constructors' Labor Council of West Virginia and Laborers' District Council of West Virginia, 2007-2009 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Code no.8913: Constructors' Labor Council of West Virginia and International Union of Operating Engineers Local 132, 2007-2009 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Code no.8934: Constructors' Labor Council of West Virginia and Mid-Atlantic Regional Council of Carpenters West Virginia District, 2007- 2009 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- Code no.8946: Ohio Contractors Association and Ohio Vicinity Regional Council of Carpenters Southwest Office and South Central Office, 2007-2010 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Code no.8959: Constructors' Labor Council of West Virginia and Operative Plasters and Cement Masons' International Association, 2006- 2009 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Code no.8963: Associated General Contractors of Indiana and Laborers' International Union of North America, Indiana District Council Local 561, 2006-2009 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- Code no.8967: Inland Northwest Associated General Contractors and Pacific Northwest Regional Council of Carpenters, 2006-2009 (Box 4, Folder 57)
- Code no.8970: Inland Northwest Associated General Contactors and International Union of Operating Engineers Local 370, 2007- 2010 (Box 4, Folder 58)
- Code no.8971: Pipe Line Contactors' Association and the United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipefitting Industry of the United States and Canada, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 59)
- Code no.8973: Inland Northwest Associated General Contractors and International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 690, 2006- 2009 (Box 4, Folder 60)
- Code no.8978: Inland Northwest Associated General Contractors and Washington & Northern Idaho District Council of laborers International Union of North America, 2006-2009 (Box 4, Folder 61)
- Code no.8995: The Builders' Association and International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers Local Union 10, 2005-2009 (Box 4, Folder 62)
- Code no.8996: Painters District Council no 2 and Painting Contactors, 2005-2010 (Box 4, Folder 63)
- Code no.9009: Mechanical Contractors Association of Western Pennsylvania and United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry of the United States and Canada Local 449, 2005-2009 (Box 4, Folder 64)
- Code no.9012: Pipe Line Contractors Association Labor Manual Revisions, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 65)
- Code no.9016: Pipe Line Contractors Association Labor Manual Revisions, 2007-2009 (Box 4, Folder 66)
- Code no.9017: Coastal International Security, Inc. and National Association of Special Police and Security Officers (NASPSO), 2005 (Box 4, Folder 67)
- Code no.9018: Coastal International Security and International Union, Security, Police and Fire Professionals of America Local 287, 2007- 2010 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Code no.9019: Knight Protective Service and UGSOA International Local 206, 2005-2008 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Code no.9023: Harrah's Laundry and Culinary Union Workers Local 226, 2008-2012 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Code no.9024: Cummins Rocky Mountain and International Union of Operating Engineers Local 428, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Code no.9025: National Electrical Contractors Association and IBEW Local 11, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Code no.9029: Fairway and UFCW Local 1500, 2007-2011 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Code no.9033: United Service Workers Union Local 455, IUJAT and United Tom-Tom Transportation Inc., 2006-2009 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Code no.9024: United Service Workers, IUJAT and Chevrolet 73, Inc., 2005-2008 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Code no.9035: United Service Workers, IUJAT, Local 455 and Weed Chevrolet Co. Inc., 2006 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Code no.9037: M.B. Consultants, Ltd. And IUJAT Local 726, 2006-2009 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Code no.9038: United Service Workers Union, IUJAT, Local 255 and United Tom-Tom Transportation Inc., 2007-2010 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Code no.9039: Interstate Waste Services Inc. and IWS Transfer Systems of New jersey, Inc. and Local 124, IUJAT, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Code no.9040: ASF-Keystone Inc. Granite City Plant and IBEW Local 309, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Code no.9041: ASF-Keystone Inc. Granite City Plant and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Pattern Makers Local 688, 2007-2010 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Code no.9042: ASF-Keystone Inc. Granite City Plant and District 9 International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 2007- 2010 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Code no.9049: Alabama Power Company and IBEW Locals 345, 833, 904, 391, 801, 841, 1053, 796, 2077, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Code no.9050: Washington Gas Light Company and International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 96, 2007-2012 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Code no.9055: Dan's Supreme Supermarkets Inc. and UFCW Local 1500, 2006-2010 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Code no.9056: King Killen Pharmacy, Inc. and UFCW Local 1500, 2006-2010 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Code no.9057: Man-Dell Food Stores Inc. and UFCW Local 1500, 2006-2010 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Code no.9060: Shoprite of Avenue 1 and UFCW Local 1500, 2006-2010 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Code no.9065: Coastal International Security Inc. and NASPSO, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Code no.9164: Southern California General Contractors and Eleven Southern California Counties Cement Masons, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Code no.9176: Continental Airlines and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Code no.9177: New United Motor Manufacturing, Inc. and UAW, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Code no.9178: MCA-SMACNA and United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipefitting Industry Local 142, 2007-2010 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Code no.9179: New York City School Construction Authority and Civil Service Technical Guild/District Council 37, 2008-2010 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Code no.9180: New York City Construction Authority and District Council 37, AFSCME Locals 154, 375, 1251, 1407, 2627, 2008- 2010 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Code no.9181: Maimonides Medical Center and New York State Nurses Association, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Code no.9182: Maimonides Medical Center and Committee of Interns and Residents/SEIU, 2007-2010 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Code no.9183: St. Vincent Mercy Center Local 12 and UAW, 2006-2009 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Code no.9184: St. Vincent Mercy Medical Center and Local 12 and UAW, 2006-2009 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Code no.9207: UAW Local 862 and Ford Motor Company Louisville Assembly Plant, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Code no.9208: Ford Motor Company and UAW Local 862, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Code no.9210: Logistics Service Inc. and UAW Local 659 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Code no.9211: Ai Flint/Genesee L.L.C. and UAW Local 659 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Code no.9213: Service and Parts Operations Flint Processing Center Division of General Motors Corporation and UAW Local 659, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Code no.9214: GM Powertrain Flint Engine South Plant and UAW Local 659, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Code no.9215: General Motors Corporation Metal Fabricating Division and UAW Local 659, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Code no.9216: Premier Manufacturing Support Services and UAW Local 659, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Code no.9217: Caravan/Knight F.M. and UAW Local 659, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Code no.(9)?219: General Motors Corporation Die Engineering Service and UAW Local 653, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Code no.9220: Dupont County Division Northeastern Illinois Chapter NECA and IBEW Local 701, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Code no.800103L Wicomico County B.O.E. and Wicomico County Education Association, 2007-2010 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Code no.800241: Minnesota State Colleges and Universities Board of Trustees and Minnesota State College Faculty, 2005-2007 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Code no.800243: Minnesota State Colleges and Universities Board of Trustees and the Inter Faculty Organization, 2005-2007 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Code no.800258: Middle Management Association and State of Minnesota, 2007-2009 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Code no.800267: State of New Hampshire and State Employees Association of New Hampshire, Service Employees International Union Local 1984, 2007-2009 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Code no.800299: State of Connecticut and Administrative and Residual Employees Union Local 4200- AFT/CFEPE, 2003-2007 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Code no.800325: State of Maine and Maine State Employees Association SEIU Local 1989, 2007-2009 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Code no.800364: State of California and CAUSE Statewide Law Enforcement Association, 2005-2008 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Code no.800372: Racine Unified School District and Racine Education Association, 2007-2009 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Code no.800378: University of Minnesota and Minnesota Teamsters Public and Law Enforcement Employees Union Local 320, 2005- 2009 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Code no.810010: Anaheim City School District BOE and Anaheim Elementary Education Association, 2007-2008 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Code no.810443: New York City and Sanitation Officers Association, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Code no.810445: Health and Hospitals Corporation and Communication Workers of America, Local 1180, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Code no.810456: New York City and United Fire Officers Association, Local 854, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Code no.812482: City of Baltimore and American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees Council 67, Local 44, 2009- 2010 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Code no.810591: New York City and Uniformed Firefighters Association, 2006-2008 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Code no.811152: New York City and Motor Vehicle Operators District Council 37, 2005-2008 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Code no.811214: Jefferson County BOE and Jefferson County Association of Educational Support Personnel, 2005-2010 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Code no.811250: New York City and Correction Officer's Benevolent Association, 2005-2007 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Code no.811314: New York City and Real Estate Titles Council 37, 2005-2008 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Code no.811415: New York City and Blue Collar Council 37, 2005-2008 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Code no.811432: New York City and Accounting & EDP Council 37, 2005-2008 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Code no.811433: New York City and Seasonals District Council 37, 2005-2008 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Code no.9165: Communications Workers of America and SBC East, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Code no.9169: Empire State Regional Council Carpenters Local 85 and Independent Contractors of Carpenters Local 85, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Code no.9170: [No Employer] and Construction and General Laborers Local 154, 2009-2010 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Code no.9171: Wendy's and Local Joint Executive Board of Las Vegas, 2005-2010 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Code no.9175: Continental Airlines Inc. and Air Line Pilots Association, 2005-2008 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Code no.811434: New York City and Health Services District Council 37, 2005-2008 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Code no.811436: New York City and Local 246, SEIU, 2005-2008 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Code no.811470: New Yok City Transit Authority and District Council 37, 2002-2005 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Code no.811808: New York City and District Council 37, 2005-2008 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Code no.811833: New York City and Engineering & Scientific District Council 37, 2005-2008 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Code no.811838: New York City and Sergeants Benevolent Association, 2003-2005 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Code no.811840: New York City and Committee of Interns and Residents, 2005-2008 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Code no.820075: Council 67, Local 44 and Baltimore City Board of School Commissioners, 2007-2009 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Code no.820080: New York City and Institutional Services Council 37, 2005-2008 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Code no.820211: County of Riverside and Laborer's International of North America Local 777, 2006-2010 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Code no.820233: Board of Regents of the University of Washington and SEIU Local 925, 2007-2009 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Code no.820256: County of Kent and United Auto Workers Local 2600, 2006-2007 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Code no.820450: Hennepin County and American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees Local 34, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Code no.820486: Hennepin County and American Federation of State, Count, and Municipal Employees Local 2822, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Code no.820670: County of Riverside and Service Employees International, Local 1997, 2006-2009 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Code no.820804: University of California and University of Professional and Technical Employees, 2007-2011 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Code no.820813: Washoe County School District and Washoe Educational Association, 2005-2007 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Code no.820827: School District of Escambia County and Escambia Education Association, 2004-2007 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Code no.820868: Poway Unified School District and Poway Federation of Teachers, 2007-2009 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Code no.830182: Memphis City Schools and American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees Local 1733, 2007- 2010 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Code no.830198: SEIU Local 500 and Montgomery County BOE, 2008-2010 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Code no.830204: Salt Lake City School District BOE and Salt Lake Teachers Association, 2007-2008 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Code no.830274: Omaha Education Association and Douglas County School District No.0001, 2005-2007 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Code no.830281: Douglas County School District 1 and Service Employees Local 226, 2006-2009 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Code no.830423: Rhode Island Hospital and International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 251 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Code no.830460: State of Maryland and AFT Healthcare Maryland, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Code no.830554: Howard County BOE and Howard County Education Association, 2007-2010 (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Code no.830555: Howard County BOE and Howard County Education Association Educational Support Professionals, 2007-2010 (Box 6, Folder 48)
- Code no.830728: Clerical, Administrative, and Professional Employees of the Classified Service of New York City and City University of New York and New York State Nurses Association, 2002-2007 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Code no.830741: Edmonds School District and Edmonds Education Association, 2007-2010 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Code no.830747: Los Angeles Community College District and Los Angeles College Faculty Guild, 2005-2008 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Code no.830751: New York City School District BOE and District Council 37, 2002-2008 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Code no.830760: Kenosha School Board and Kenosha Education Association, 2007-2009 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Code no.830774: Manatee County District School Board and Manatee Education Association 3821, 2007-2010 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Code no.830787: Fort Wayne Community Schools and Fort Wayne Education Association, Inc., 2007-2009 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Code no.830790: American Federation of Teachers and San Diego Community College District, 2005-2008 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Code no.830792: Jordan Classified Professional Association and Jordan School District, 2008-2009 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Code no.830793: Livonia BOE and Livonia Educational Administrators and Livonia Education Association, 2006-2009 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Code no.830813: Davenport Community School District and Davenport Education Association, 2008-2009 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Code no.830836: University of California and University Council American Federation of Teachers, 2007-2010 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Code no.830842: University of California and American Federation of State County and Municipal Employees, 2005-2008 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Code no.830844: University of California and California Nurses Association, 2005-2007 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Code no.840012: New York City and Correction Captains Association, 2007-2012 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Code no.840030: New York City Transit Authority and Civil Service Technical Guild, 2002-2005 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Code no.840114: McLaren Regional Medical Center and American Federation of State County and Municipal Employees Local 2650, 2006- 2010 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Code no.840115: McLaren Regional Medical Center and International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 332, 2005-2009 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Code no.840116: Ingham Regional Medical Center and Office and Professional Employees International, 2006-2009 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Code no.840117: Ingham Regional Medical Center and Office and Professional Employees International, 2005-2008 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Code no.840119: New York City and Chaplains District Council 37, 2005-2008 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Code no.840120: New York City and District No.1-PCD/MEBA Licensed Division, 2006-2008 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Code no.840121: New York City and District Council 37, 2002-2006 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Code no.840122: New York City and Local No.3, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 2006-2008 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Code no.840123: Connecticut State Board of Education and American Federation of School Administrators Local 61, 2007-2011 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Code no.840124: Affiliated Faculty of Emerson College and Emerson College, 2004-2008 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Code no.840125: Macon-Piatt Regional Office of Education and American Federation of State County and Municipal Employees Council 31, 2006-2007 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Code no.840127: United Service Workers Local 255 and Borough of Middlesex, 2006-2008 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Code no.840128: Borough of South River and United Service Workers Local 255, 2006-2009 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Code no.840129: Township of Old Bridge and Old Bridge Public Works and Sanitation, 2004-2009 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Code no.840131: City of Baltimore and American Federation of State County and Municipal Employees, 2009-2010 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Code no.[Unknown]: Minneapolis Automobile Dealers' Association and International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 974, 2006- 2009 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Code no.[Unknown]: Southern California Edison Company and IBEW Local 47, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Code no.[Unknown]: Building Material Teamsters Local 282 and New York City Heavy Construction and Excavating Industry, 2006- 2009 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Code no.[Unknown]: Board of Trustees of Michigan Affiliated Healthcare System, Inc. and Office and Professional Employees International Local 459, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Code no.[Unknown]: Pres. Ken Bordieri for the Union and Mr. William H. Ives for the Company, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Code no.543854: Shulman, Rogers, Gandal, Pordy, & Ecker, PA and Maps of Michigan, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 37)